Guide to the Cornell University Department of Natural Resources records, 1909-1995.
Cornell University Department of Natural Resources records, 1909-1995.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cornell University Department of Natural Resources records, 1909-1995.
21-18-991
Cornell University. Dept. of Natural Resources.
24.5 cubic ft.
Reports, bulletins, field notes, slides, radio talks, publications, photographs, drawings, and subject files.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library.
Includes annual reports, monthly reports, bulletins, plans of work, field notes, slides of Cornell campus and activities, radio talks, publications, photographs, committee records, drawings, subject files, and other materials of the Cornell University Department of Natural Resources, formerly the Conservation Department.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes annual reports, monthly reports, bulletins, plans of work, field notes, slides of Cornell campus and activities, radio talks, publications, photographs, committee records, drawings, subject files, and other materials of the Cornell University Department of Natural Resources, formerly the Conservation Department. Also, 1939 report on land use in Arnot Forest and slides and photographs used in a 1983 master's thesis by Wayne Hartz.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University.; Hartz, Wayne.; Cornell University. Conservation Dept.
Subjects:
Conservation of natural resources.
Form and Genre Terms:
Drawings.; Photographs.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Mainly radio talks (indexed), c. 1930-late 1940's (Box 1)
- Department of Conservation binders of mimeos and publications (Box 1-2)
- Alphabetical A-Z by subjects (Box 3-4)
- County Agents or people at random (not alphabetized); Also 4-H Material (Box 5-8)
- Geneva Maple Syrup Reports, Tressler and Wheeler, 1943; 1 (Box 9)
- Circular No. 182 - Geneva - The Painting of Sap Buckets and Other Equipment Used in the Production of Maple Syrup, July 1, 1938; 2 (Box 9)
- Bulletin No. 699 - Geneva - Three Years' Operation of an Experimental Sugar Bush, Tressler and Zimmerman, January 1942; 3 (Box 9)
- Bulletin No. 720 - Geneva - Factors in the Preparation of Maple Cream, F.W. Hayward, March 1946; 4 (Box 9)
- Journal of Agriculture Research - The Preparation and Painting of Maple-Sugar - Producing Equipment, Willits and Tressler, July 15, 1939; 5 (Box 9)
- Ture L. Johnson - Correspondence - F.E. Winch, Jr., 6 (Box 9)
- Motion Pictures - Maple Syrup, 7 (Box 9)
- Ernest Johnson - Meteorologist - Weather Broadcasting - Maple Syrup - Correspondence F.E. Winch, Jr., 8 (Box 9)
- Tour - Maple Syrup, 1958 and back; 9 (Box 9)
- Research - Maple Syrup, 10 (Box 9)
- Statistics - Maple Syrup, 11 (Box 9)
- Maple Projector - E.H. Jones, 1951; 12 (Box 9)
- Publicity - Maple Syrup, 13 (Box 9)
- Stow Manufacturing Company - Correspondence - F.E. Winch, Jr., 14 (Box 9)
- 4-H Maple Syrup Record, 15 (Box 9)
- Proposed Questions for Maple Syrup Meetings, 16 (Box 9)
- New York's Changing Maple County - Winch, 17 (Box 9)
- Wisconsin Maple Production, 18 (Box 9)
- Roger W. Pease, West Virginia University - Maple Syrup, 19 (Box 9)
- Dr. P.A. Wells, Maple Syrup Conference, November 13-15, 1950; 20 (Box 9)
- Vermont - Maple Correspondence, 21 (Box 9)
- New Hampshire - Maple Syrup, 22 (Box 9)
- Michigan - Maple Syrup, 23 (Box 9)
- "Canadian" Maple Letters, 24 (Box 9)
- Maple Syrup - NYS Agricultural Experiment Station, Geneva, 25 (Box 9)
- J.F. Sproul - Sproul Hwd. and Manufacturing Company, Delevan, NY, 26 (Box 9)
- Maple Syrup Report, 27 (Box 9)
- Percision Thermometer and Instrument Company, Philadelphia, PA, 28 (Box 9)
- Taylor Instrument Company, Rochester, NY, 29 (Box 9)
- Rochester Manufacturing Company, 30 (Box 9)
- Cornell University - Maple Syrup Folder, 31 (Box 9)
- Cost Accounts - Maple Syrup, 32 (Box 9)
- New York Maple Festival, 1956-1957; 33 (Box 9)
- Grading Laws - Grades - Maple Syrup, 34 (Box 9)
- Maple Syrup Meetings, 1950-1951; 35 (Box 9)
- Maple Products, 36 (Box 9)
- Marketing Maple Products, 37 (Box 9)
- Costs and Returns in Producing and Marketing Maple Products by Robert D. Bell, December 1955; 38 (Box 9)
- Wyoming County Maple Producers Association, 39 (Box 9)
- Maple Producers, 1954; 40 (Box 9)
- Charles F. Hager, Sec. New York Maple Producers Association - Correspondence - F.E. Winch, Jr., 41 (Box 9)
- Western New York Maple Producer's Association, 42 (Box 9)
- New York Maple Producer's Association, William Churchill, President, 43 (Box 9)
- Pennsylvania Maple Products, 44 (Box 9)
- Central New York Maple Producer's Association, 45 (Box 9)
- Lloyd Sipple - Correspondence - F.E. Winch, Jr., 46 (Box 9)
- Northern New York Maple Producer's Association, 47 (Box 9)
- Producer's Records - Maple Syrup, 1958 and back; 48 (Box 9)
- Steam Boiler - Mark Sanford - Cope, 49 (Box 9)
- Sugar Bushes - Maple Syrup - Cope, 50 (Box 9)
- Don G. Limbert - Correspondence - Josh Cope, 51 (Box 9)
- Maple Syrup Supplies, 52 (Box 9)
- Chemicals for Cleaning Equipment, 53 (Box 9)
- Seaplant Chemical Corporation "SeaKem", 54 (Box 9)
- Bakelite Plastics - Tubing, 55 (Box 9)
- Irvington Varnish and Insulator Div. Minn. Min. and Mann. Co., 56 (Box 9)
- Maple Can Inquiry, 57 (Box 9)
- American Can Company - Cope, 58 (Box 9)
- C.W. Aeppler Company m.s., 59 (Box 9)
- Binghamton Glass Company, 60 (Box 9)
- Continental Can Company, Inc., Rochester, New York, 61 (Box 9)
- Containers and Labels, 62 (Box 9)
- Maple Packaging - Dobeckmun Company, 63 (Box 9)
- Stern Can Company - Peabody, Massachusetts, 64 (Box 9)
- Sugar Bush Supplies Company - Lansing, Michigan, 65 (Box 9)
- Upressit Products Corp. Danburz, Connecticut, 66 (Box 9)
- Eastern Can Company, 67 (Box 9)
- Kotpel Filter Paper Company - Chicago, Illinois, 68 (Box 9)
- Visking Corporation, 69 (Box 9)
- Leader Evaporator Company, Inc. - Vermont, 70 (Box 9)
- Evaporators, 71 (Box 9)
- Leader Evaporator Company - Burlington, Vermont, 72 (Box 9)
- Lightening Evaporator Company - Richford, Vermont, 73 (Box 9)
- Vermont Evaporator Company - Ogdensburg, NY, 74 (Box 9)
- The Cleveland Twist Drill Company - Maple Syrup, 75 (Box 9)
- Greenlee Manufacturing Company - Rockford, Illinois, 76 (Box 9)
- Power Tapping Equipment - Maple Syrup, 77 (Box 9)
- Thermometer - Maple Syrup, 78 (Box 9)
- The Story of the 1952 NYS 4-H Conservation Training Camp, 79 (Box 10)
- Conservative Camp Construction Donation Funds, 80 (Box 10)
- Kitchen Records, 81 (Box 10)
- Arnot - Reports to Council, etc., 82 (Box 10)
- Arnot - Notes General, 83 (Box 10)
- Arnot - Construction - General, 84 (Box 10)
- Arnot Cabins, 85 (Box 10)
- Arnot 4-H Camp Project Plans, 86 (Box 10)
- Arnot Gifts and Acknowledgements, 87 (Box 10)
- Arnot History, 88 (Box 10)
- Arnot Camp 4-H, 1964; 89 (Box 10)
- First Annual Cornell Conservation Leadership School, 1963-1964; 90 (Box 10)
- Arnot 4-H Business, 1964; 91 (Box 10)
- Arnot Electrical, 92 (Box 10)
- Central Building - Materials lists, 93 (Box 10)
- Arnot Kitchen Elec., 94 (Box 10)
- Arnot Development 63-64, 95 (Box 10)
- Arnot - Central Building Interior Construction and Equipment, 96 (Box 10)
- Arnot - Kitchen, 97 (Box 10)
- Camp Arnot - Food Planning, 98 (Box 10)
- Arnot Business, 1963; 99 (Box 10)
- Arnot Business, 1964, 100 (Box 10)
- Cabin Plan, Wyomoco - 4-H and Arnot, 101 (Box 10)
- Central Building Est. - Dept. Health Approvals, 102 (Box 10)
- Central Building - gifts, 103 (Box 10)
- Arnot Campaign - swimming pool, 104 (Box 10)
- American Agriculturist, 105 (Box 10)
- Agricultural Leaders Digest, 106 (Box 10)
- American Forests - Ovid Butler, Editor, 107 (Box 10)
- The American Home, 108 (Box 10)
- Better Farming Methods, 109 (Box 10)
- Rural New York, 110 (Box 10)
- Saturday Evening Post, 111 (Box 10)
- Successful Farming, 112 (Box 10)
- "Wood", 113 (Box 10)
- Maryland Foresters, 114 (Box 10)
- Massachusetts Park Association, 115 (Box 10)
- McKee Hybrid Poplars, 116 (Box 10)
- The Northeastern Logger, 117 (Box 10)
- The New York Lumber Trade Journal, 118 (Box 10)
- New York Forester, 119 (Box 10)
- Massachusetts Farm Magazine, 120 (Box 10)
- "Forest Notes" Concord, New Hampshire, 121 (Box 10)
- Journal of Forestry, 122 (Box 10)
- Hoard's Dairyman, 123 (Box 10)
- Forest Products Journal, 124 (Box 10)
- The Farm Quarterly, 125 (Box 10)
- Farm Journal, 126 (Box 10)
- Country Gentlemen, 127 (Box 10)
- The Conservationist, 128 (Box 10)
- Capper's Farmer, 129 (Box 10)
- Buffalo Evening News, 130 (Box 10)
- Binghamton Press, 131 (Box 10)
- Better Farms Magazine, 132 (Box 10)
- Forestry Regional Field Day, 133 (Box 10)
- William J. Gabriel, Res. Forester, NE Experiment Station, 134 (Box 10)
- Hemlock Arboretum "Far Country", 135 (Box 10)
- Ralph Hosmer, 136 (Box 10)
- Claude Heit - Geneva - Seed Testing, 137 (Box 10)
- Coopersburg Handle Works, 138 (Box 10)
- American Fork and Hoe Co., 139 (Box 10)
- Compensation (Insurance), 140 (Box 10)
- Brush Control, 141 (Box 10)
- Cotton Hanlon, 142 (Box 10)
- Sam Daniels Manufacturing Company, 143 (Box 10)
- Doyle Cumulative Volume Table Data, 144 (Box 10)
- Mid-Hudson Forest Products Co-operative, Inc., 145 (Box 10)
- J.H. Monteath Company, 146 (Box 10)
- O'Dell and Eddy Victor Treyz Company, 147 (Box 10)
- Planning Mill Blades, 148 (Box 10)
- C. Prouty and Company, 149 (Box 10)
- Splitting Guns, 150 (Box 10)
- Manufactures of Tree Planters, 151 (Box 10)
- Land Grant Associations, 152 (Box 10)
- Tree Planting Services Publication, 153 (Box 10)
- New York State Museum, 154 (Box 10)
- Farm and Home Week, 1955; 155 (Box 10)
- Farm and Home Week, 1956; 156 (Box 10)
- Farm and Home Week, 1957; 157 (Box 10)
- Farm and Home Week, 1954; 158 (Box 10)
- Plan of Work - Department of Conservation, 1953-1959-1964; 159 (Box 11)
- Forestry and Wildlife Project Reports, 1955; 160 (Box 11)
- Articles for Extension News Press, etc. - Cunningham, 161 (Box 11)
- 4-H Conservation Project, 162 (Box 11)
- Cornell Extension Publications - Old Copy, 163 (Box 11)
- Conservation Project II, 4-H Club, 164 (Box 11)
- Plan of Work, 1967,1970; 165 (Box 11)
- Quebec 4-H Forestry, 166 (Box 11)
- Jeffers Farm (Christmas Tree), 167 (Box 11)
- Collection of Forest Appreciation Projects, 1945-1949; 168 (Box 11)
- Cornell Economic Land Classification Leaflet 1,; Economic Classification of Rural Land Broome Co., New York Pasto and Conklin, October 1949; 169 (Box 11)
- L.R. Simons - Director of Extension (Old Correspondence), 170 (Box 11)
- C. Harrington - Extension State Leaders Office, 171 (Box 11)
- Osage Orange - General Information, 172 (Box 11)
- Personnel - General, 173 (Box 11)
- A Forest Co-op Goes Scandinavian, 174 (Box 11)
- Dean Palm - College of Agriculture, 175 (Box 11)
- Articles for Publication - Dickson, 176 (Box 11)
- Reprints, 177 (Box 11)
- State 4-H Club Congress, 178 (Box 11)
- Conservation Training School, 1956-1957; 179 (Box 11)
- Agent Workshop, 1957; 180 (Box 11)
- Camp Oswegatchie - State FFA Camp, 181 (Box 11)
- 4-H Regional Forestry Field Days, 182 (Box 11)
- Forestry Field Days, Southeastern, NY, 183 (Box 11)
- Forestry Field Days, Eastern, 1944; 184 (Box 11)
- Collection Book Completions, 1950-1952; 185 (Box 11)
- National 4-H Club Congress, 186 (Box 11)
- Conservation Workshops, 1953; 187 (Box 11)
- Revised 4-H Projects, 188 (Box 11)
- Pilot Woodland Management Program, 189 (Box 11)
- Onondaga Complex Planning (FE Winch), 190 (Box 11)
- Pack Demonstration Forest, 191 (Box 11)
- Articles for issue of New York Forester, November 1968; 192 (Box 11)
- New York State Conservation Dept. Bureau of Nurseries - Summary of Tree Distribution by Species, 1945-1960; 193 (Box 11)
- Magazine Articles - Extension, April 1959-October 1960; 194 (Box 11)
- Webster's Woodlot - Alex Dickson, 195 (Box 11)
- Improving the FPA Foresters Public Image - Winch, 196 (Box 11)
- A 4-H Project in the Study of Population Dynamics of the New York State Songbird - The Bluebird, 197 (Box 11)
- The Future Role of Christmas Trees in Land Use II - E.L. Stone, 198 (Box 11)
- Multiple - Use Management of the Christmas Tree Farm - Winch, 199 (Box 11)
- Planting Trees for ...? Dickson, January 1974; 200 (Box 11)
- Trees as Forest Products - Winch Radio, March 1971; 201 (Box 11)
- Acid Rain - Northern New York and New England, 202 (Box 11)
- Trees and Water - Dickson, 203 (Box 11)
- Selling Your Timber - Dickson, 204 (Box 11)
- Private Forestry in New York State - Dickson, 205 (Box 11)
- Timber Agent Program Expanded - Dickson, 206 (Box 11)
- Be a Tree Detective - Dickson, 207 (Box 11)
- It's the Heartwood That Counts - Dickson, 208 (Box 11)
- Draw Up a Contract -- When You Sell Timber - Dickson, 209 (Box 11)
- Radio Interview with Frank Liguori, Tompkins County Planner - Dickson, 210 (Box 11)
- A Fall Crop - Free - F.E. Winch, 211 (Box 11)
- Forest Planning in New York - Should We Be Involved? - Winch, 212 (Box 11)
- Trends in Maple Production in New York - Winch, 213 (Box 11)
- The Energy Crisis and the Woodlot - Winch, 214 (Box 11)
- Gypsy Moths - Will It Be a Universal Pest? - Winch, 215 (Box 11)
- The Energy Crisis vs. Wood Fuel - Winch, 216 (Box 11)
- Conifers Damaged by Highway Salt - Winch, 217 (Box 11)
- Forestry and Chautauqua County - Winch, 218 (Box 11)
- Environmental Concerns in Snow and Ice Control with Salt - Winch, 219 (Box 11)
- Selling Your Christmas Trees - Dickson, 220 (Box 11)
- Plan Your Spring Tree Planting Now - Dickson, 221 (Box 11)
- Ecological Impact of Snow and Ice Control Methods - Winch, 222 (Box 11)
- The Forest Areas of Ithaca, 223 (Box 11)
- Forest, Wither Goeth Thou - Winch, 224 (Box 11)
- Alex Dickson - Third PR Short Course, - Welcome, May 8, 1972; 225 (Box 11)
- NY-PA Short Course, April 4-5, 1972; 226 (Box 11)
- National Parks vs. National Forests - Winch, 227 (Box 11)
- Maple Syrup- Winch, 1974; 228 (Box 11)
- Know Your Trees - Winch, 229 (Box 11)
- 4-H Wood Sample Collection - "Woods of New York" - Winch, 230 (Box 11)
- Planting Forest Trees in Rural NY - Morrow, Winch, and Hamilton #1161, 231 (Box 11)
- Private Camp Grounds as an Alternative Use of Land - Holcomb, Concklin, Winch, 232 (Box 11)
- Mechanizing the Small Farm Woodlot - Foss and Winch, 233 (Box 11)
- Outdoor Cookery Bulletin - Winch, 234 (Box 11)
- Motivation Studies - Small Woodland Owners - Winch, 235 (Box 11)
- Shaping Christmas Trees for Quality - G.R. Cunningham and Winch, 236 (Box 11)
- Growing and Marketing Christmas Trees - Winch, 237 (Box 11)
- Bacterial Control for Higher Quality Sap - Winch, 238 (Box 11)
- Radio Talks - Winch, 239 (Box 11)
- Maple Syrup Production in NYS - Raymond and Winch, 240 (Box 11)
- Bob Ames - Articles for Farm and Home News - Comm. Arts, 241 (Box 11)
- Judging Maple Products - Manuscript - Winch et al., 242 (Box 11)
- Maple Syrup and Other Maple Products (revised manuscript) - Winch and Morrow, 243 (Box 11)
- Manuscript - Maple Bulletin - Winch, 244 (Box 11)
- Vo-Ag Teachers Summer School - Program, July 16-30, 1965; 245 (Box 12)
- Subject Matter Training School for Assistant County Agriculture Agents, 1962; 246 (Box 12)
- New Specialists Induction Program, September 9-10, 1964; 247 (Box 12)
- Agents In-Service Training Committee, 248 (Box 12)
- County Agriculture Agents Training School - General File, 249 (Box 12)
- Agriculture Agents Induction School, 250 (Box 12)
- Subject Matter Training School for Assistant County Agricultural Agents, 1954-1960; 251 (Box 12)
- Subject Matter Training School for Assistant County Agricultural Agents, 1961; 252 (Box 12)
- Subject Matter Training School for Extension Agents - Agriculture Division, 1967; 253 (Box 12)
- Subject Matter Training School for Extension Agents - Agriculture Division, 1966; 254 (Box 12)
- In-Service Training Program for New Extension Field Staff - Ag. Div., 255 (Box 12)
- Subject Matter Training School for Assistant County Agricultural Agents, 1964; 256 (Box 12)
- Subject Matter Training School for Assistant County Agricultural Agents, 1963; 257 (Box 12)
- Extension Staff Minutes, 1963-1967; 258 (Box 12)
- Cope Correspondence, 1944; 259 (Box 12)
- Old Photos, 260 (Box 12)
- Winch Publications, 261 (Box 12)
- New York State Annual Report of Forestry - Extension Work, 1924-1926 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- New York State Annual Report of Forestry - Extension Work, 1926-1927 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- New York State Annual Report of Forestry - Extension Work, 1927-1928 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Annual Report of the Extension Forester, 1928-1929 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Annual Report of the Extension Forester, 1929-1930 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Annual Report of the Extension Forester, 1930-1931 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Annual Report of the Extension Forester, 1931-1932 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Annual Report of the Extension Forester, 1932-1933 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Annual Report of the Extension Forester, 1933-1934 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Annual Report of the Extension Forester, 1934-1935 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Annual Report of the Extension Forester, 1935-1936 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Annual Report of the Extension Forester, 1936-1937 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Annual Report of the Extension Forester, 1937-1938 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Annual Report of the Extension Forester, 1938-1939 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- A Brief Report of the Development and Growth of the Forestry Project in New Yokr State, 1912-1939 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Annual Report of the Extension Forester, 1939-1940 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Annual Report of the Extension Forester, 1940-1941 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Annual Report of the Extension Forester, 1941-1942 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Annual Report of the Extension Forester, 1942-1943 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Annual Report of the Extension Forester, 1943-1944 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Annual Report of the Extension Forester, 1943-1944 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Annual Report of the Extension Forester, 1944-1945 (Box 13, Folder 22)
- Annual Report of the Extension Forester, 1945-1946 (Box 13, Folder 23)
- Annual Report of the Extension Forester, 1946-1947 (Box 13, Folder 24)
- Annual Report of the Extension Forester, 1947-1948 (Box 13, Folder 25)
- Annual Report of the Extension Project #13, 1948-1949 (Box 13, Folder 26)
- Annual Report of the Extension Project #13, 1949-1950 (Box 13, Folder 27)
- Annual Report of the Extension Project #13, 1950-1951 (Box 13, Folder 28)
- Annual Report of the Extension Project #13, 1951-1952 (Box 13, Folder 29)
- Annual Report - New York State Agricultural Extension Service, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 30)
- Annual Report - New York State Agricultural Extension Service, 1954 (Box 13, Folder 31)
- Annual Report - New York State Agricultural Extension Service, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 32)
- Annual Report - New York State Agricultural Extension Service, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 33)
- Annual Report - New York State Agricultural Extension Service, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 34)
- New York State College of Agriculture - Plan of Work, 1925-1935 (Box 13, Folder 35)
- New York State College of Agriculture - Plan of Work, 1935-1942 (Box 13, Folder 36)
- New York State College of Agriculture - Plan of Work, 1942-1947 (Box 13, Folder 37)
- New York State College of Agriculture - Plan of Work, 1925-1951 (Box 13, Folder 38)
- Plan of Work - Department of Conservation, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 39)
- Plan of Work - Conservation Project #13, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 40)
- Plan of Work - Conservation Project #13, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 41)
- Plan of Work - Conservation Project #13 - 5-Yr Plan, 1959-1964 (Box 13, Folder 42)
- Analysis of the Problems of Silviculture and Forest Planting - Behre, 1940 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Conservation at Cornell, 1940-1961 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Essex County Forest Farming Project under Cooperative Farm Forestry Act, 1941 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- 4-H Flotsam, 1933-1935 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- "Meals and Nights in the Open", 1941 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- New York State Farm Forestry Plan - Soil Conservation Service-Region 1, Oct-39 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Plot Inspection Notebooks - Book A, Book B Copy 1, 1937-1040 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Plot Inspection Notebooks - Book A, Book B Copy 2, 1937-1940 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Remeasurement of Demonstration Plots - Books A, B, C, E, 1934-1938 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Silviculture Report on Woodland Areas, [1935] (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Survey of the Wood-Using Industries of Broome, Chemung and Tioga Counties - New York, June-29 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- U.S. Census of Agriculture - New York Counties, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Wood Lot Improvement - Books 1, 2, 5, 6, 1927-1929 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Wood Lot Improvement - Books 11-14, 1933-1939 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- New York State Woodsmen's Field Days - No. 30, No. 31, 1977, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Maps of New York State Showing Forest Districts - 4 copies (Box 15)
- Maps of New York State - Town Maps for Bedford through Yorktown (Box 15)
- Maps of New York State - Highway Survey Committee - USGS Quadrangles (Box 15)
- Index Map of USGS Quadrangles (Box 15)
- 2X2 Color Slides - Campus Scenes, Buildings, People [#1-#110 - Missing 13, 30, 36, 50, 63, 64, 77, 86, 101, 103, 105, 107] (Box 15)
- New York State Christmas Tree Growers' Association, Inc., 1957; 1 (Box 16)
- Cooperative Extension Work Agreements, 1960-1961; 2 (Box 16)
- New York State Forest Practice Board, 1957-1962; 3 (Box 16)
- Arnot Committee, 1957-1958; 4 (Box 16)
- Arnot Teacher's Training Camp, 1957, 1961; 5 (Box 16)
- Broome County Development Committee, 1956-1963; 6 (Box 16)
- County Commodity Committees Outlines, 1961; 7 (Box 16)
- Conservation Needs Committee, 1957-1958; 8 (Box 16)
- C.F.M. Conference, 1961; 9 (Box 16)
- Tree Farm Inspection Program, 10 (Box 16)
- Resource Information Laboratory, 1973-1974; 11 (Box 16)
- Pole Type Structures, 1950-1954; 12 (Box 16)
- Wood Preservation - Small Custom Plants, 13 (Box 16)
- Wood Preservation Statistics, 1949-1959; 14 (Box 16)
- Connecticut Hill Reconnaissance, 1924; 15 (Box 16)
- Mapleton Woodlot, 1956; 16 (Box 16)
- Sherburne Red Oak Plantation, 17 (Box 16)
- Picard Hardwood Plantation, 1940; 18 (Box 16)
- Ogden Hardwood Plantation, 1940; 19 (Box 16)
- Arnot Meteorological Data, 1929-1932; 20 (Box 16)
- Adirondack Forestry Tour, 1933; 21 (Box 16)
- Adirondack Forestry Tour, 1934; 22 (Box 16)
- Adirondack Forestry Tour, 1935; 23 (Box 16)
- Adirondack Forestry Tour, 1936; 24 (Box 16)
- 1937 Adirondack Forestry Tour, 25 (Box 16)
- 1938 Adirondack Forestry Tour, 26 (Box 16)
- Resource Development - NY, MI, MA, 27 (Box 16)
- Improved Harvesting Mehtods (USDA), 1948-1958, 28 (Box 16)
- Central States Forest Experiment Station, 1948-1953, 29 (Box 16)
- Communication Training - Extension, 1963-1964, 30 (Box 16)
- 4-H Staff, 1957-1958, 31 (Box 16)
- Farm Forestry Committee, 1954-1961, 32 (Box 16)
- Rural Areas Development, 33 (Box 16)
- Small Woodlot Dvelopment, 34 (Box 16)
- Luther Preserve, 1923-1928, 35 (Box 16)
- Forest Service/Extension Information, 36 (Box 16)
- Outdoor Recreation, 37 (Box 16)
- Extension - Consolidated Progress Statement, 1961-1962, 38 (Box 16)
- Analysis of Extension Program in Farm Forestry, 39 (Box 16)
- Forestry and Farm Loans Information, 40 (Box 16)
- NY State Tree Planting Data, 1960, 41 (Box 16)
- NYS DEC Foresters' Training Conference, 42 (Box 16)
- Changes in Farming, 1967, 43 (Box 16)
- Wood Preservatives - General, 44 (Box 16)
- Wood Preservatives - Creosote, 45 (Box 16)
- Wood Preservatives - Cuprinol, Inc., 46 (Box 16)
- Wood Preservatives - Copper Naphthenates, 47 (Box 16)
- Wood Preservatives - Cromated Zinc Clhoride, 48 (Box 16)
- Wood Preservatives - Pentachlorphenol I, 49 (Box 17)
- Wood Preservatives - Pentachorphenol II, 50 (Box 17)
- Wood Preservatives - Penta - Dow Chemical Co., 51 (Box 17)
- Wood Preservatives - Penta - Monsanto Chemical Co., 52 (Box 17)
- Uses of Woods, 53 (Box 17)
- Orienteering, 54 (Box 17)
- Mordoff Woodlot, 55 (Box 17)
- Map of McLean Preserve, 56 (Box 17)
- Blight Resistant Chestnut, 57 (Box 17)
- Pruning Notes, 58 (Box 17)
- Black Ash Projects, 1934-1938, 59 (Box 17)
- White Ash - Dave Cook, 60 (Box 17)